

www.trangerthings.com www.behance.net/trangtt42714e5 trangtt427@gmail.com (925) 352-3373



# PROFILE

A creative thinker with 7+ years of combined UX design, visual design and print experience. I like to approach design issues with the capacity of a user, thinking about the best ways to communicate a business goal in the simplest form.



#### EXPERIENCE

## Controlco - UX Designer/Front End Developer

September 2016 - October 2017

- Collaborated with a building automations team to create IoT applications, both mobile and desktop, for clients to control facility operational settings.
- Designed and developed dashboards, alarm consoles, and other entities to track building innerworkings using HTML/CSS, some javascript, Niagara 4 and DGLux5.
- Designed interfaces that allowed clients to interact with cloud data from installed equipment.
- Provided wireframes, user storyboards, mock-ups, and prototypes using tools like Sketch, InVision, Photoshop, and Illustrator.

# VSL - Visual Designer

August 2015 - July 2016

- Created digital assets as a part of the Vintage Senior Living brand.
- Came up with website architecture and flow.
- Worked with marketing team to design print collateral that adhered to company design guidelines.

### Freelance - Graphic Designer

August 2008 - Current

- Design both digital and print collateral using Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign.
- Ideate and provide artistic critique of client ideas.
- Create digital paintings and scalable graphics.

#### Mt. Diablo High School - Digital Arts Tutor

August 2008 - December 2010

- Taught sophomores how to use Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop), Flash, and Final Cut.
- Challenged students to come up with ideas and solutions to proposed issues in design.
- Mentored students and provided artistic critiqe in coursework.
- Managed classroom digital equipment.



# EDUCATION

# University of California, Santa Barbara 2012 - 2014

B.S. Biology, emphasis in psychobiology

## Diablo Valley College 2008 - 2012

A.A. Biology
Other focuses: graphic design,
painting with watercolors,
2D animation, architecture,
psychology



#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

#### Skills

Gathering data Lo-fi & hi-fi mock-ups

Wireframing & storyboarding

Iterative design

Prototyping

HTML/CSS

Print design

Visual design

Color theory

Typography

Iconography

#### Software

Sketch

InVision

Photoshop

Illustrator

InDesign

CorelDRAW

AutoCAD

Final Cut

SketchUp

Maya

### Hobbies

Drawing

Photography

Traveling

Petting cats

Re-designing websites for fun